amung.us 2019-12-31

# whos.amung.us - privacy policy

(This statement is only available in our official website language of English) 

**Our Commitment to Your Privacy**   
At whos.amung.us Inc. your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we have provided this notice explaining our online information practices. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where any personally identifiable information (PII) may be requested and/or collected. whos.amung.us Inc. reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time without notice. This privacy policy only affects whos.amung.us and other sites, services, and domains operated by whos.amung.us Inc. it does not pertain in any manner to any websites linking to whos.amung.us (or related domain, operated by whos.amung.us Inc.), or any websites linked to from a whos.amung.us Inc. site or domain. 

whos.amung.us Inc. does not collect any personally identifiable information - except where noted below. 

Data is collected in the following ways: 

  * **Free widget services**   
You will not be required to provide any personally identifiable information, or any information at all, should you choose to install one of our free widgets on your website in order to utilize our statistics services. You, and any user who visits a website containing a whos.amung.us Inc. free widget, will be providing an IP address, page URL reference(s), and browser/operating system information in the request header. This is a standard HTTP request header and is available freely to the operator of any website you choose to visit. We, and/or our partners, may log certain aspects of this header and/or data as part of our services. We, and/or our partners, may log certain aspects of the content where our widgets are installed, as well as non-personally identifiable actions users may take on these sites/pages (such as a copy action). 
  * **Subscription based Pro widget service**   
In order to effectively provide our subscription based Pro service we require owners of websites who wish to use our services provide relevant information for contact and billing purposes only, this may include, but is not limited to: names, addresses, emails, zip/postal code information, phone numbers, billing information, etc. In addition to the information collected by the above free widget service, Pro widgets may collect information from you or any visitor to a site containing a Pro widget, such as user operating system and browser. Again, this information is derived from a standard HTTP request header and is available freely to the operator of any website you choose to visit. We, and/or our partners, may log certain aspects of this header and other information collected via Javascript as part of our services, no personally identifiable information is collected, or released to any third party. We, and/or our partners, may log certain aspects of the content where our widgets are installed, as well as non-personally identifiable actions users may take on these sites/pages (such as a copy action). 
  * **Advertising and all other business relationships**   
Any person, company, or entity choosing to enter into an advertising and/or other business relationship with whos.amung.us Inc. will be required to provide any necessary personally identifiable information in order to complete the business transaction/relationship. This information may include, but is not limited to: names, addresses, phone numbers, server information, email addresses, trademarks and copyrights used in and advertising capacity. 

**Privacy Policy Requirements**   
By using any of our services you agree to have and abide by an appropriate privacy policy and will comply with all applicable laws relating to the collection of information from visitors to your website(s). It is your responsibility to take any action required to uphold regulatory requirements and inform your users adequately that your website(s) use third party technology and cookies that assist in collection and sharing of anonymous NPII for the purpose of analytics and advertising. You must post a privacy policy and that policy must provide notice of your use of cookie(s) and/or services that collects non personally identifiable (NPII) traffic data. You may wish to add a link to the whos.amung.us privacy policy (this page) in order to improve transparency and empower user's choice, where an opt out mechanism is made available. 

**IP Address Usage**   
Every computer and device connected to the Internet is assigned a unique number known as an Internet protocol (IP) address. Since these numbers are usually assigned in country-based blocks, an IP address can often be used to identify the country, region and city from which a computer is connecting to the Internet. Like other web traffic analytic service providers, whos.amung.us collects the IP address of website visitors in order to provide website owners with a general idea of where in the world their visitors come from, this is known as geolocation. Regardless of a website owners usage of whos.amung.us, or other analytic services, they have access to IP addresses for visitors to their website(s). We anonymize IP addresses in our systems by zeroing the last octet out. 

**Cookies, Web Beacons & Partners**   
whos.amung.us Inc. may place cookies on your system in order to provide a better and more informative service to our users. A cookie is simply a small text file stored by your browser that is sent by your browser to the corresponding site that originally set the cookie (ie. cookies are only available to the site that originally set them). These cookies may include, but are not limited to, user preference information and unique user IDs for internal tracking purposes. No personally identifiable information (PII) will be contained in these cookies. 

Some of our partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site, products, or services. Our partners include, but are not limited to, Google. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, telephone number, or any other personally identifiable information) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about these practices, used by Google, or to opt out of having cookies set on your system, please visit [Google's Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) page. 

These third-party partners, ad servers, or ad networks may power the services, advertisements, and links that appear, or are used on whos.amung.us and any of its services. Because your web browser must request this data from the third party’s servers, those companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their website directly. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs, but no personally identifiable information is transmitted. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party partners to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

whos.amung.us Inc. has no access to or control over these cookies or other technology that are used by third-party advertisers or partners.   
While we require our partners to uphold this privacy policy, we do not monitor or control such third parties cookies and accordingly we are not responsible or liable in any manner to the type of information collected by such third parties cookies. If you would like to file a compliant regarding such third party activity you can Contact Form.   
We are not responsible for any of the content published on supply Partners’ websites.   
We may offer in our documentation and/or website partners’ summaries, logos and links to their websites and third party publications and/or websites may refer or link to our website; this should not be seen as notice of affiliation, endorsement, authorization or representation. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party partners and ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. You may wish to opt out of bahviorally targeted advertising by using the the opt out mechanisms at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>. The whos.amung.us Inc. privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers, partners, or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

Our technology aims to improve relevance of online advertising and offer a more personalized experience to users. Certain non-personal user information may used for the matter in order to improve advertisement relevance and revenue on your website. whos.amung.us may engage in business relationships with partners that would grant these parties access to non-personally identifiable information (NPII) data collected by whos.amung.us and/or provide these parties with product integration with whos.amung.us products. While the data whos.amung.us collects is non-personally identifiable (NPII), third party partners may use this data to behaviourally target ads or improve ad relevence. whos.amung.us ensures all partners engaged respect opt out wishes for ad targeting, you can learn more about what ad networks have set cookies on your system and opt out of them using the NAI's opt out mechanism at: 

We currently work with the following partners to provide certain aspects of our services, they have their own opt out mechanisms: 

**Disclosure**   
We may share some or all of your information (personally identifiable (PII), which is not available unless you explicitly make it available to us, and non personally identifiable (NPII)) with our subsidiaries, joint ventures or other companies under a common control that we have or may have in the future, or such third parties that acquire us or substantially all of our assets, providing such party undertakes to protect your privacy in accordance with these terms. Otherwise, we will not disclose your personal information to any third party, unless: 

  * Required to do so as part of any legal proceedings conducted between you and whos.amung.us.
  * Required to do so by court order.
  * In case the activity of the Website/Technology is transferred to a third party, providing such party undertakes to protect your privacy in accordance with these terms.

Any information collected by whos.amung.us Inc. will be held in a secure manner to the fullest of our abilities; however whos.amung.us Inc. does not take any responsibility for any third party unauthorized access to our servers, offices, computers, or other information containing stores. Access to any information we collect is granted only to whos.amung.us Inc. employees, agents, partners, or authorized contractors. whos.amung.us may retain non personalliy identifiable information (NPII) data on its servers for a period of twenty (20) days prior to compressing and aggregating it to the point it could not be associated with a specific site visit. 

Neither its data Partners nor whos.amung.us collect or store sensitive information such as personally identifiable information other than IP addresses. No data related to political, ethnic or racial origins, philosophical, sexual or religious orientation, health condition, financial condition, children under the age of 13 and other sensitive categories. 

By using this website and/or our services you agree to this privacy policy and agree to indemnify whos.amung.us Inc. of any claims, demands, or actions resulting from a breach of this privacy policy. 

whos.amung.us Inc. may update this privacy policy at any time. The date of last change will be posted on this page alongside the modified privacy policy. 

This above privacy policy was last updated: May 24, 2018. 

You may wish to opt out of our services by clicking the link below. Opt out preferences are stored in a cookie so if you clear your cookies you will need to opt out at this page again. Since the cookie is specific to this browser you may wish to opt out on all browsers you use. When you opt out information about your visit will not be recorded in the stats of any site you visit that utilizes our services (this covers both Free and PRO services). 

Current opt out status: not opted out [opt out]. 

If you have any questions please do not hesitate to contact us. 

Contact Form.
